//set questions array object
var questions = [
  {
    Question: 'In the year 1900 in the U.S. what were the most popular first names given to boy and girl babies?',
    Choices: ['A. William and Elizabeth', 'B. Joseph and Catherine', 'C. John and Mary', 'D. George and Anne'],
    Answer: 'C. John and Mary'
  },
  {
    Question: 'When did the Liberty Bell get its name?',
    Choices: ['A. when it was made, in 1701', 'B. when it rang on July 4, 1776', 'C. in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery', 'D. none of the above'],
    Answer: 'C. in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery'
  },

  {
    Question: "In the Roy Rogers -Dale Evans Museum, you will find Roy and Dales stuffed horses. Roy's horse was named Trigger, which was Dales horse?",
    Choices: ['A. Buttermilk', 'B. Daisy', 'C. Scout', 'D. Tulip'],
    Answer: 'A. Buttermilk'
  },

  {
    Question: 'The Daniel Boon museum at the home where he died can best be described how?',
    Choices: ['A. a log cabin in Kentucky', 'B. a two-story clapboard house in Tennessee', 'C. a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri', 'D. a three story brick house in Arkansas'],
    Answer: 'C. a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri'
  },

  {
    Question: 'Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?',
    Choices: ['A. home computer', 'B. compact disk player', 'C. cordless phone', 'D. dishwasher'],
    Answer: 'B. compact disk player'
  },

  {
    Question: 'Who holds the record for the most victories in a row on the professional golf tour?',
    Choices: ['A. Jack Nicklaus', 'B. Arnold Palmer', 'C. Byron Nelson', 'D. Ben Hogan'],
    Answer: 'C. Byron Nelson'
  },

  {
    Question: 'Who is third behind Hank Aaron and Babe Ruth in major league career home runs?',
    Choices: ['A. Reggie Jackson', 'B. Harmon Killebrew', 'C. Willie Mays', 'D. Frank Robinson'],
    Answer: 'C. Willie Mays'
  },

  {
    Question: 'In 1990, in what percentage of U.S. married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?',
    Choices: ['A. 8', 'B. 18', 'C. 38', 'D. 58'],
    Answer: 'B. 18'
  },

  {
    Question: 'During the 1980s for six consecutive years what breed of dog was the most popular in the U.S.?',
    Choices: ['A. cocker spaniel', 'B. German shepherd', 'C. Labrador retriever', 'D. poodle'],
    Answer: 'A. cocker spaniel'
  },

  {
    Question: 'In 1985, five percent of U.S. households had telephone answering machines. By 1990 what percentage of homes had answering machines?',
    Choices: ['A. 10 percent', 'B. 15 percent', 'C. 31 percent', 'D. 51 percent'],
    Answer: 'C. 31 percent'
  },

  {
    Question: 'The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?',
    Choices: ['A. Frederick Douglass', 'B. Booker T. Washington', 'C. Louis Armstrong', 'D. Joe Louis'],
    Answer: 'D. Joe Louis'
  },

  {
    Question: 'What did the "D" in "D-Day" stand for?',
    Choices: ['A. doom', 'B. day', 'C. Dwight (Eisenhower)', 'D. Dunkirk'],
    Answer: 'B. day'
  },

  {
    Question: 'The Brownie Box Camera introduced by Eastman Kodak in 1900 had a retail price of what?',
    Choices: ['A. $1', 'B. $5', 'C. $10', 'D. $20'],
    Answer: 'A. $1'
  },

  {
    Question: 'Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?',
    Choices: ['A. Charlie Brown', 'B. Bugs Bunny', 'C. Mickey Mouse', 'D. Fred Flintstone'],
    Answer: 'A. Charlie Brown'
  },

  {
    Question: 'The Philadelphia mint started putting a "P" mint mark on quarters when?',
    Choices: ['A. 1960', 'B. 1980', 'C. never'],
    Answer: 'B. 1980'
  },

  {
    Question: "Before becoming George Bush's Secretary of Defense, what was Dick Cheney's position?",
    Choices: ['A. congressman from Wyoming', 'B. governor of New Hampshire', 'C. secretary of defense under Ronald Reagan'],
    Answer: 'A. congressman from Wyoming'
  },

  {
    Question: 'When Mt. St. Helens erupted on May 18, 1980, how many people were killed?',
    Choices: ['A. 1', 'B. 57', 'C. 571'],
    Answer: 'B. 57'
  },

  {
    Question: 'In J. Edgar Hoover, what did the J stand for?',
    Choices: ['A. James', 'B. John', 'C. Joseph'],
    Answer: 'B. John'
  },

  {
    Question: 'Florence Nightingale became known as "the Lady With the Lamp" during which war?',
    Choices: ['A. American Civil War', 'B. Crimean War', 'C. World War I'],
    Answer: 'B. Crimean War'
  },

  {
    Question: 'What year was it that the Census Bureau first reported that a majority of new mothers  were remaining in the new job market?',
    Choices: ['A. 1968', 'B. 1978', 'C. 1988'],
    Answer: 'C. 1988'
  }
];
